Contact

8801718139997 (Mobile) sakhawathossain82@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sakhawat-hossain-34aa51129 (LinkedIn)

Languages

English & Bangla (Professional Working)

Sakhawat Hossain

Manager, Admin and Operations, Triple Bonded Services Ltd, (One of the business wings of Bay Group)

Summary

I am a Citizen Of Bangladesh by birth, Place of birth is Sirajganj. Now I am working as Sr. Executive, HR & Admin at Bay Group, one of the leading business group in Bangladesh dealt with Leather Processing, Footwear Manufacturing, Infrastructure Development, Chemical Supplying and Industrial Engineering business.

Most recently I have worked as Junior Officer (Contingent worker) in HSBC Bd. Ltd, One of the World Wide leading Bank through Smart Services Ltd (SSL).

Previously I have worked as Junior Officer (Contingent worker) in Lever Brothers Bd. Ltd (Unilever), Grameen Phone, Aktel (Robi), Paxco Ltd through Integrated Security Services Ltd.

Specialties: I am able to work in a Team with target & under pressure. I am sound in Office Administration, Office Management & Operations, repair maintenance, Vendor Management, Store Management, Foreign affairs, Protocol, deal with Land/ Flat Owner-Law enforces Agencies, Event Management. Passport, Visa & Ticketing.

I have more trhan14 years working Experience in some of National & international Organizations in Bangladesh.

Experience

Triple Bonded Services Limited, Bay Group Manager, Admin & operations
January 2020 - Present (5 months)
Kawran Bazar, Dhaka-1215

Admin and operation related all issues handling. Guest House maintaining.

Arrange VISA, Air Ticket, Protocol, Food & accommodation for Staff & Guests.

Arrange all kind of Logistics support as & when necessary.

Bay Group Sr. Executive, HR & Admin December 2015 - December 2019 (4 years 1 month)

H-18, Alaol Avenue, Sec-06, Uttara, Dhaka-1230

HR & Admin related all Tasks

SSL-Smart Services Limited (Work Station - HSBC, Management Office, Tejgaon, Dhaka)
Junior Officer
November 2014 - November 2015 (1 year 1 month)
Tejgaoun, Dhaka

ISSL-Integrated Security Services Limited (Served as Contingent Employee in GP, Robi, HSBC)
Junior Officer
December 2002 - October 2014 (11 years 11 months)
Junior Officer

Education

Jagannath University College MSS, Political Science · (2004 - 2005)